Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
Center for Digital Research in the Humanities University of Nebraska–Lincoln
- Records of the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia; Law, Appellate, and Criminal Records; Case Papers 1802-1863
  - April, Civil Trials, 710-835, 1823 (Box 289)
  - April, Civil Trials, 837-951, 1823 (Box 290)
  - April, Civil Trials, 954-1339, Negroes Lucy & Matilda v. G. Mason & Alexander Moore; 1823,; petition for freedom; Black Washingtonians says H. Mitchell instead of Alexander Moore (Box 291, Folder 1309)
  - April, Civil Trials, 954-1339, Negro Milly v. B. Warring & J. Gantt; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 291, Folder 1330)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Tilghman Mitchell; 1823,; "for selling as a slave a negro held to service for a term of years" (Box 292, Folder 10)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Peter Pike; 1823,; "a coloured man, for receiving stolen goods" (Box 292, Folder 17)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. William Shorter; 1823,; "a colored man, for an assault and battery on Sarah Gray, a colored woman" (Box 292, Folder 37)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Nancy Ashton; 1823,; "negro, for a Violent Assault & Battery..." (Box 292, Folder 69)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Harry Hanson; 1823,; "negro,...for stealing a piece of cloth" (Value $3.00) (Box 292, Folder 75)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. William James; 1823,; "a free Negroe," for stealing "one pair of pantaloons, one shirt and one cravat" (Value $2.00) (Box 292, Folder 77)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. William James; 1823,; for stealing "one watch, one shirt and one cravat" (value $25.00) (Box 292, Folder 79)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Thomas Shorter; 1823,; "negro, for stealing a pair of shoes" (Value $1.00) (Box 292, Folder 88)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Michael Loman, Dora Johnson, "negro," and Henry Williams, "negro"; 1823,; for stealing (a) "two drab great coats & one hat" (Value $14.00) and (b) "one pair of Jefferson boots" (Value $2.00); the only remarkable feature of these cases is that Loman, whose race is unidentiﬁed, presumably was white (Box 292, Folder 89-91 and 95-97)
  - April, Criminal Appearances, U.S. v. Jane Jasper; 1823,; "negress,...for having stolen a pair of lead colored Morocco shoes" (Value 75 cents) (Box 292, Folder 107)
  - April, Appeals, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1823 (Box 293)
  - April, Imparlances, Recognizances, U.S. v. Kitty; 1823,; "a free mulatto woman alias Kitty Rutherford" John van Riswick suspects "that a certain Kitty Rutherford did last night steal from him his negro boy George"—she seems to be connected with William Rutherford, who is the subject of Recognizance 26 (a $100 peace bond)—since William Rutherford is not identiﬁed by race, we may assume that he was white (Box 294, Folder 29)
  - April, Judicials, 2-130, William I. McCormick v. Brooke M. Berry; 1823,; "one negro boy called Robert about 14 years old" $200.00 (Box 295, Folder 85)
  - April, Judicials, 131-278, Elijah Parsons v. John Goszler; 1823,; "...the following personal property that is to say, one horse and cart—one negro man named Tom and one negro girl [‘woman’ crossed out] named Mary—and all household furniture..." (Box 296, Folder 155)
  - April, Judicials, 330-478, 1823 (Box 297)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Joseph Burke v. Rachel Hoskins; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 21)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Basil Wells v. Ignatius Young; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 25)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Nace Humphreys, Jr. v. William Berry; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 33)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Wood Humphreys v. William Berry; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 34)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Nace Humphreys v. John B. Lambert; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 35)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Nace Humphreys v. John Boswell; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 38)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, James Humphreys v. Henry Roberts; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 39)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Susan Smith v. Thomas Johns; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 59)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Richard Johnson v. Janet Lingan; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 74)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 2-144, Richard Luckett v. Janet Lingan; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 298, Folder 75)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 146-274, Negro Patty v. Charles Ratcliffe; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 299, Folder 175)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 146-274, Jane Sims v. Benjamin King; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 299, Folder 202)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 146-274, Esther Humphreys v. John B. Lambert; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 299, Folder 233)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 276-515, Z. Hazle v. W. Smith & S. Black; 1823,; "l Negro woman Rachael" $200.00 (Box 300, Folder 306)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 276-515, George A. Goszler v. Tench Ringgold; 1823,; "one negro man named Tom" $300.00 "one negro Girl named Mary" $300.00 (Box 300, Folder 312)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 276-515, Isaac Owens v. George Tyler; 1823,; "Rose a Negro woman aged 45 years" $ 50.00 "Negro Susan aged about 12 years" $200.00 (Box 300, Folder 350)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 276-515, Mary Hughes v. C.W. Boteler; 1823,; "one Negro boy about ten years of age" $ 75.00 (Box 300, Folder 471)
  - October, Civil Appearances, 518-852, 1823 (Box 301)
  - October, Civil Trials, 1-353, Negro Fanny and children v. Thomas Quandell; 1823,; petition for freedom; Black Washingtonians says Quantrill (Box 302, Folder 4)
  - October, Civil Trials, 1-353, Nicholas L. Queen v. James Middleton; 1823,; "cofﬁn for Black man" $5.00 (Box 302, Folder 323)
  - October, Civil Trials, 356-457, Dennis Wright v. E. Robinson & R. Taylor; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 303, Folder 416)
  - October, Civil Trials, 356-457, Negro Amelia v. E.B. Caldwell; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 303, Folder 417)
  - October, Civil Trials, 460-604, Ann E. Payton v. Henry B. Robertson; 1823,; "one Negro man Named Jerry" $450.00 "one Negro woman Named Sally" $300.00 (Box 304, Folder 562)
  - October, Civil Trials, 606-678, 1823 (Box 305)
  - October, Civil Trials, 680-770, 1823 (Box 306)
  - October, Civil Trials, 771-849, 1823 (Box 307)
  - October, Civil Trials, 853-980, William Berry v. James Symington; 1823,; petition for freedom; Petition to release from indenture. (Box 308, Folder 867)
  - October, Civil Trials, 983-1076, Peregrine Warﬁeld v. Samuel Harrison; 1823,; Doctor’s bill (treating slaves) $ 93.25 (Box 309, Folder 1039)
  - October, Civil Trials, 983-1076, Negro Lucy and child v. Clement Smith; 1823,; petition for freedom (Box 309, Folder 1076)
  - October, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, 1823 (Box 310)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negess Caroline; 1823,; theft two dollars (money) (Box 311, Folder 48)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negress Jane Eliza Waine; 1823,; theft clothing worth $9.25 (Box 311, Folder 57)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro William Graham; 1823,; "did kill Negro Edward Johnson by shooting him" (Box 311, Folder 63)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Hemy Hanson; 1823,; theft one pair of shoes worth $1.75 (Box 311, Folder 68)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Leonard Butler; 1823,; theft one quilt and clothing worth $6.00 (Box 311, Folder 79)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Philip Sims; 1823,; theft cloth worth 75 cents (Box 311, Folder 83)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Eliza Paine; 1823,; theft clothing worth $43.25 (Box 311, Folder 86)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Jos. Turner; 1823,; theft cloth worth $20.00 (Box 311, Folder 90)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Charles Cole; 1823,; assault and battery (on a white man?) (Box 311, Folder 93)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Charles Johnson; 1823,; theft two hats worth $16.00 (Box 311, Folder 104)
  - October, Inquests, Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1823; "Miscellaneous" ﬁle "We the Grand Jurors for the body of the County aforesaid, do on our oaths present, the rapid increase of free people of colour within the said county, as an evil which requires the interference of the Legislative authority." [undated] (Box 311, Folder rough bundle)
  - October, Imparlances, Judicials, 1-59, 1823 (Box 312)
  - October, Judicials, 60-178, 1823 (Box 313)
  - October, Judicials, 180-322, 1823 (Box 314)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Joseph Burke v. Rachel Hoskins; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 39)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Nace Humphreys, Jr. v. William Berry; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 41)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Wood Humphreys v. William Berry; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 42)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Nace Humphreys v. John B. Lambert; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 43)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Nace Humphreys v. John Boswell; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 53)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, James Humphreys v. Henry Roberts; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 54)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Susan Smith v. Thomas Johns; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 72)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Richard Johnson v. Janet Lingan; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 81)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Richard Luckett v. Janet Lingan; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 82)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 1-160, Negro Patty v. Charles Ratcliffe; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 315, Folder 138)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 162-391, Esther Humphreys v. John B. Lambert; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 316, Folder 173)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 408-740, 1824 (Box 317)
  - April, Civil Trials, 1-312, 1824 (Box 318)
  - April, Civil Trials, 329-489, J. Pearson & R.Y. Brent v. I.Y. Young; 1824,; names, ages and individual valuations of twelve slaves, male and female, aged 3 to 35 years, worth in all $2150; names, ages and individual valuations of four slaves, male and female, aged 48 to 64 years, worth in all $70 ("carpr. Michael" was worth $40; the others, $10 each) (Box 319, Folder 450)
  - April, Civil Trials, 329-489, Kitty Shorter and her infant children v. Daniel Rapine; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 319, Folder 471)
  - April, Civil Trials, 329-489, William Jordan v. Lemuel Sawyer; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 319, Folder 472)
  - April, Civil Trials, 329-489, Lucy Oakley and her infant children v. Asa E. Hough; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 319, Folder 473)
  - April, Civil Trials, 495-645, Fanny Tarlton v. Cartwright Tippett; 1824,; petition for freedom (Box 320, Folder 555)
  - April, Civil Trials, 647-726, Mordecai Martin v. Henry W. Ball; 1824,; clothing and hire of "man Tom" (1 yr.) $151.74 (Box 321, Folder 649)
  - April, Civil Trials, 729-815, 1824 (Box 322)
  - April, Civil Trials, 819-909, 1824 (Box 323)
  - April, Civil Appearances, 911-1005, 1824 (Box 324)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1824; "Miscellaneous" ﬁle "Reed of Jeremiah McKenzie two hundred and thirty ﬁve dollars in full satisfaction for a certain Negrow girl Named Eliza—about 18 years of age" (Box 325, Folder rough bundle)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro John Mason; 1824,; for stealing "divers knives and forks" Worth $20.00 (Box 325, Folder 27)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro James Brown; 1824,; "one cart load of rails" worth $1.00 (Box 325, Folder 45)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro William Davis; 1824,; one horse worth $40; saddle & bridle worth $10.00 (Box 325, Folder 50)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Leonard Butler; 1824,; "three raw hides" worth $6.00 (Box 325, Folder 52)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Henry Hanson; 1824,; assault and battery on Charles Moody (Box 325, Folder 55)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Henry Jenkins; 1824,; coat and hat worth $1.00 (Box 325, Folder 71)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, U.S. v. Negro Betsy Johnson; 1824,; silk scarf worth $1.50; piece of ribbon worth $2.50 (Box 325, Folder 73)
  - April, Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, US. v. Negro Betsy Johnson; 1824,; 12-15 yds calico worth $2.00 (Box 325, Folder 74)
  - April, Imparlances, Judicials, 4-97, 1824 (Box 326)
  - April, Judicials, 99-297, 1824 (Box 327)
  - April, Judicials, 319-504, 1824 (Box 328)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, John Bacchus Burvill v. William Melvin; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 43)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, George Hunter v. William M. & Zadock Offutt; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 58)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Milley Bowie v. William M. & Zadock Offutt; 1824, December; petition for freedom; Black Washingtonians says "Millie" (Box 329, Folder 59)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Jospeh Burke v. Rachel Hoskins; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 101)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Nace Humphreys, Jr. v. William Berry; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 102)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Wood Humphreys v. William Berry; 1824, December (Box 329, Folder 103)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Nace Humphreys v. John B. Lambert; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 104)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Nace Humphreys v. John Boswell; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 108)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, James Humphreys v. Hemy Roberts; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 109)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Susan Smith v. Thomas Johns; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 121)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Richard Johnson v. Janet Lingan; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 130)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Richard Luckett v. Janet Lingan; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 131)
  - Civil Appearances, 2-165, Negro Patty v. Charles Ratcliffe; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 329, Folder 164)
  - Civil Appearances, 167-365, Esther Humphreys v. John B. Lambert; 1824, December; petition for feedom (Box 330, Folder 188)
  - Civil Appearances, 374-763, Negro Rebecca and her children v. Lloyd Pumphrey; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 331, Folder 424)
  - Civil Appearances, 374-763, Gill Litchworth v. Zadok Wilson; 1824, December; petition for freedom; Black Washingtonians says "Letchworth" (Box 331, Folder 523)
  - Civil Trials, 1-100, Milford Foote v. John B. Armstead; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Civil Trials, 102-274, 1824, December (Box 333)
  - Civil Trials, 276-460, J. Hooff v. E. Patterson & S. Smoot; 1824, December; "hire of my boy John" 8 months @ $15 $120.00 "Clothing of servant boy John which they omitted to furnish him with" 30.00 (Box 334, Folder 355)
  - Civil Trials, 465-620, 1824, December (Box 335)
  - Civil Trials, 625-760, 1824, December (Box 336)
  - Civil Trials, 763-880, Negro Rebecca and her children v. Lloyd Pumphrey; 1824, December; petition for freedom (Box 337, Folder 880)
  - Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Negro Fielder Gantt; 1824, December; larceny (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Negro H Smith; 1824, December; larceny (Box 338, Folder 9)
  - Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Negro Joe Butler; 1824, December; assault and battery (Box 338, Folder 42)
  - Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Negro Henry Hanson; 1824, December; larceny one pair of shoes worth $1.50 (Box 338, Folder 44)
  - Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Negro Margaret Smith; 1824, December; receiving stolen goods worth $5.00 (Box 338, Folder 46)
  - Appeals, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Negro Julia Williams; 1824, December; larceny clothing worth $5.00 banknotes worth $100.00 (Box 338, Folder 55)
  - Imparlances, 1824, December (Box 339)
  - Recognizances, Rough Bundle, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1824, December; Unnumbered, dated 9/28/24 "To the Marshall of the district of Columbia: I commit to your custody a free colored woman, by name Araminta, on a charge of larceny...." (Box 340)
  - Judicials, 3-140, Trueman Tyler v. George B. Magruder; 1824, December; 9 slaves (5 male, 4 female), ages seven and up appraised Value, $2000.00 (Box 341, Folder 38)
  - Judicials, 141-232, 1824, December (Box 342)
  - Judicials, 233-502, A.R. Dennott v. H.W. Ball; 1824, December; "1 negro man named James, about 30 years old" $300.00 (Box 343, Folder 268)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 2-155, Negress Eliza v. William Hayman & John Wetzell; 1825,; petition for freedom (Box 344, Folder 18)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 2-155, James Hutton v. William I. Belt; 1825,; petition for freedom (Box 344, Folder 31)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 2-155, George Hunter v. William M. & Zadok Offutt; 1825,; petition for freedom (Box 344, Folder 71)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 2-155, Milly Bowie v. William M. & Zadok Offutt; 1825,; petition for freedom; not found (Box 344, Folder 27)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 160-370, 1825 (Box 345)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 379-485, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Fielder Gantt; 1825,; stealing "one raw hide" worth $3.00 (Box 346, Folder 4)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 379-485, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Henry Smith; 1825,; stealing "one coat" worth $20.00 (Box 346, Folder 5)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 379-485, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Jim Tyler; 1825,; assault and battery on Betsey Becket (Box 346, Folder 45)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 379-485, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. James Price; 1825,; stealing "one blue cloth coat" worth $7.00 (Box 346, Folder 46)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 379-485, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Jim Tyler; 1825,; housebreaking (Becket’s house) (Box 346, Folder 57)
  - May, Civil Appearances, 379-485, Criminal Appearances, Criminal Trials, U.S. v. Calvin Richards; 1825,; stealing three pairs of shoes worth $3.00 (Box 346, Folder 7)
  - May, Civil Trials, 3-250, Negro Leanna and child v. Lloyd Pumphrey; 1825,; petition for freedom; not in box? (Box 347, Folder 98)
  - May, Civil Trials, 3-250, Prince Gray v. Joel T. Gustine; 1825,; petition for freedom; not in box?; Black Washingtonians says Joel T. Gaskins (Box 347, Folder 100)
  - May, Civil Trials, 3-250, Prince Gray v. Catharine Linn; 1825,; petition for freedom; not in box? (Box 347, Folder 105)
  - May, Civil Trials, 254-414, 1825 (Box 348)
  - May, Civil Trials, 416-516, 1825 (Box 349)
  - May, Civil Trials, 518-617, 1825 (Box 350)
  - May, Civil Trials, 619-705, Appeals, Recognizances, 1825 (Box 351)
  - May, Imparlances, Rough Bundle, 1825; Habeas corpus ﬁle Petition of George Griffin, "a free man of colour" (Box 352, Folder rough bundle)
  - May, Judicials, 1-275, Negro Rebecca and children v. Lloyd Pumphrey; 1825,; petition for freedom (Box 353, Folder 197)
  - May, Judicials, 1-275, U. S. v. Negro Joe Butler; 1825,; "Pardoned by the President of the United States" (Box 353, Folder 212)
  - May, Judicials, 277-452, Titlings for Executions, Titlings for Writs, 1825 (Box 354)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-171, Daniel Jones v. James R. Bosley; 1825, December; petition for freedom (Box 355, Folder 45)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-171, George Hunter v. W.M. & Z. Offutt; 1825, December; petition for freedom (Box 355, Folder 80)
  - Civil Appearances, 1-171, Milly Bowie v. W. M. & Z. Offutt; 1825, December; petition for freedom; Black Washingtonians says "Millie" (Box 355, Folder 81)
  - Civil Appearances, 175-517, 1825, December (Box 356)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Mulatto Jack Kendall; 1825, December; assault and battery (Box 357, Folder 17)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro Jane Smith; 1825, December; stealing "4 silver tea spoons" worth $2.00 (Box 357, Folder 38)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro Jack Coneck; 1825, December; stealing a blanket worth $3 and "1 pr pantaloons" worth $2 (Box 357, Folder 42)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro Henry Thomas; 1825, December; stealing 1 box tea worth $30 and 1 box candles worth $3.50 (Box 357, Folder 44)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro Mary Bruce; 1825, December; assault and battery (Box 357, Folder 46)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, US. v. Negro Mary Gibson; 1825, December; stealing a ﬁve-dollar bank note (Box 357, Folder 47)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro Melinda Cozer; 1825, December; stealing kitchenware worth $200 (Box 357, Folder 48)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro James Belﬁeld; 1825, December; assault and battery (Box 357, Folder 49, 60)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro James Harris; 1825, December; stealing two horses worth $100.00 (Box 357, Folder 54)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, US. v. Negro Paul Jones; 1825, December; stealing four bottles of "antique oil" worth $1.00 (Box 357, Folder 57)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro James; 1825, December; stealing two dollars and change (Box 357, Folder 62)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, US. v. Negro John; 1825, December; stealing two dollars and change (Box 357, Folder 63)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. Negro Ben Wheeler; 1825, December; stealing $1.50 in silver (Box 357, Folder 67)
  - Civil Appearances, 524-598, Appeals, Criminal Appearances and Trials, U.S. v. N.H.V. Bennett; 1825, December; includes coroner’s inquest accusing "Eliza Hicks, a Mulatto woman," of infanticide—"Geo Robinson a Coloured man took the Child from under the House while it was yet warm but was dead" (Box 357, Folder 80)